Finding Aid for Ross School of Business (University of Michigan) Publications 1916-2013
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Ross School of Business Administration (University of Michigan) Publications 1916-2013
University of Michigan. School of Business Administration.
49.6 MB
22 linear feet
Includes addresses, annual reports, bibliographies, brochures and pamphlets, bulletins and college catalogs, directories, manuals, newsletters, programs, proposals, reports, statistics, and yearbooks. Also contains publications from the Bureau of Business Research, Center for International Business Education, Division of Research, Executive Education Center, Program in International Business and the Public Utility Executive Program. Also includes conference publications from meetings held at the university and sponsored or co-sponsored by the School of Business Administration. There are also some publications describing various development campaigns and the Summer Session. Also includes the publication entitled "Dividend". Some publications (or their successors) may no longer be available in print. but are available the school's website.
00132 Bimu C221 2
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The records of the Ross School of Business were received in three major accessions, 1980, 1983 and 1993. Donor no. 6468.
The records are open for research.
See the finding aid for the Ross School of Business (University of Michigan) Records for a historical sketch of the Business School.
The Ross School of Business Publications, 1925-1998, and are divided into four series: Unit Publications, Sub-Unit Publications, Topical Publications and Student Organization Publications. The publications include addresses, annual reports, bibliographies, brochures and pamphlets, bulletins and college catalogs, directories, manuals, newsletters, programs, proposals, reports, statistics, and yearbooks. Also contains publications from the Bureau of Business Research, Center for International Business Education, Division of Research, Executive Education Center, Program in International Business and the Public Utility Executive Program. Also includes conference publications from meetings held at the university and sponsored or co-sponsored by the Ross School of Business Administration. There are also some publications describing various development campaigns and the Summer Session. Also includes the publication entitled "Dividend". Some publications (or their successors) may no longer be available in print but are available on the school s website.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Graduate School of Business Administration.; University of Michigan. Ross School of Business.; University of Michigan--Alumni and alumnae.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs.
Contributors:
University of Michigan. Bureau of Business Research.; University of Michigan. Center for International Business Education.; University of Michigan. Ross School of Business. Division of Research.; University of Michigan. Executive Education Center.; University of Michigan. Program in International Business.; University of Michigan. Public Utility Executive Program.; University of Michigan. Graduate School of Business Administration.
Genre/Form:
Addresses.; Annual reports.; Bibliographies.; Catalogs, College.; Directories.; Manuals.; Newsletters.; Pamphlets.; Programs.; Proposals.; Reports.; Statistics.
- Unit Publications
  - Abstracts
    - Personnel Management Abstracts, 1978 v. 24 (Box 1)
  - Addresses
    - Annual Business Leadership Lecture
      - 1958-1972, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Annual William K. McInally Memorial Lecture
      - 1966-1994, 1996, 8 folders (Box 1)
    - Cornerstone Laying Ceremony 1947 (Box 1)
    - Corporate Governance: Major Issues for the 1990s, 1989 (Box 1)
    - The Frontier Revisited: General Management Challenges in a Mature Industry, 1978 (Box 1)
    - General Agents' Accelerated Development Program 1978 (Box 1)
    - The Major Problem of Inflation, 1948 (Box 1)
    - The New Face of Capitalism, 1961 (Box 1)
    - A New Tax Structure for the United States, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Social Responsibilities of Business Education, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Materials
    - MBA Program 1985-2002 (scattered dates) (Box 21)
  - Annual Reports
    - Highlights
      - 1992-2002 (Box 1)
    - The Michigan Business School Annual Report
      - 1984-1991, 5 folders (Box 1)
    - Annual Report 2002 (Box 22)
  - Bibliographies
    - Faculty Bibliography
      - 1972/73-1989, 18 folders (Box 1)
    - Faculty Research and Selected Publications, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Research at the Michigan Business School (Box 2)
      - 1990-1991, 1993, 3 folders (Box 2)
      - 1994 (Box 22)
      - 1995 (Box 22)
      - 2000 (Box 22)
  - Brochures
    - 1953-1992 (Box 2)
    - Accounting Program 1963, undated (Box 2)
    - Annual Business Conference 1966-1975 (Box 2)
    - Blue Cross Executive Program: Management Development Program 1952-1953, undated (Box 2)
    - Career Series 1951 (Box 2)
    - Dearborn Center 1960-1961 (Box 2)
    - Highlights, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
    - Joint Degree Programs undated (Box 2)
    - MBA Evening Program 1966-1969, undated (Box 3)
    - Management Programs, July 1984-June 1985, undated (Box 3)
    - Master of Business Administration 1963-1971 (Box 3)
    - The Michigan BBA 1985, 1986, undated (Box 3)
    - The Michigan MBA 1982/83-1985/86, undated, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - The Michigan Ph.D. 1966, 1982/83, 1999-2003, undated (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous undated, 1946-1991, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Ph.D. Program in Statistics and Management Science undated (Box 3)
    - Program in Quantitative Methods undated (Box 3)
    - Public Finance Institute 1974-1979 (Box 3)
    - Secretarial 1963-1964 (Box 3)
    - The William A. Paton Center for Accounting Education and Research undated (Box 3)
    - circa 2000-2002 (Box 22)
  - Bulletins
    - Announcement, Undergraduate and Graduate Programs
      - 1922/1923-1954/1955 (Box 3)
    - Graduate Program
      - 1955/56-1985/86, 16 folders (Box 3)
      - 1987/88-1994/95, 4 folders (Box 4)
      - 1995-1999, 2002 (Box 4)
      - 2004 (Box 4)
    - Graduate Program
      - 2004-2005, .PDF file
      - 2005-2006, .PDF files
      - 2006-2007, .PDF files
      - 2007-2008, .PDF files
      - 2008-2009, .PDF files
      - 2009-2010, .PDF files
      - 2010-2011, .PDF files
      - 2011-2012, .PDF files
      - 2012-2013, .PDF files
    - Graduate Evening Program 1993-2002, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Graduate Executive Program 2002 (Box 4)
    - Graduate Full-Time Day Program 1992 (Box 4)
    - Graduate Part-Time Program 1993 (Box 4)
    - Undergraduate Program
      - 1955/56-1999 2002 (Box 21)
      - 2004-2005, .PDF files
      - 2005-2006, .PDF files
      - 2006-2007, .PDF files
      - 2007-2008, .PDF files
      - 2008-2009, .PDF files
      - 2009-2010, .PDF files
      - 2010-2011, .PDF files
      - 2011-2012, .PDF files
      - 2012-2013, .PDF files
  - Doctoral Program 1994-1997, 2001/02
  - Directories
    - Alumni Bulletin 1924-1943, 1943 (Box 4)
    - Alumni Directory
      - 1983 (Box 4)
      - 1986 (Box 4)
    - Business School Student Directory, 1988/89, 1997/98 (Box 4)
    - BBA Graduates, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Directory of Ph.D. Graduates 1935-1993, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Doctoral Candidates, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
    - Doctoral Candidates: Placement Roster, 1970-1978 (Box 4)
    - Entering BBAs, MAccs, MBAs, Entering and Continuing Ph.Ds, Faculty and Staff
      - 1984-1990, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Faculty and Staff, 1946-1981, 1994 (Box 5)
    - First Year MBA, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
    - 40th Anniversary: Class of 1937, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration BBAs: Entering Class, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration: Entering MBAs, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration MAcc: Entering Class, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration MBAs: Entering Class
      - 1979-1983, 5 folders (Box 5)
    - Holders of the Degree of Doctor of Philosophy in Business Administration, 1968 (Box 5)
    - MBA Graduates, 1977 (Box 5)
    - MBA '78, 1978 (Box 5)
    - New Faculty, 1988/89-1989/90 (Box 5)
    - Ph.D. Alumni Directory
      - 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Ph.D. Alumni Directory, 1935-1987, 1935-1993, 1935-1995 (Box 5)
    - Ph.D. Directory, 1965-1979 (Box 5)
    - Photo Directory (Graduate), 1973/74-1974/75 (Box 5)
    - Resume Book of the Entrepreneur Club, 1984 (Box 5)
    - School of Business Administration BBAs: Entering Class, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Specialists, [ca. 1991] (Box 5)
    - Who's New
      - 1960-1979, 4 folders (Box 5)
  - Flyers
    - 1998 undated (Box 5)
  - Invitations
    - 1975-1998, undated (Box 5)
  - Manuals
    - Graduate Student Handbook
      - 1973-1975, 1995/96 (Box 6)
    - Guide to Computing Resources at the Graduate School of Business Administration, University of Michigan, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Library Guide for Students, undated (Box 6)
    - Undergraduate Student Handbook
      - 1973-1975, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Doctoral Recognition Program 2004-2006 (Box 22)
    - In Memory, Professor Andy Andrews 2002 (Box 22)
    - MBA Perspectives, undated (Box 22)
    - Michigan Business School Publication Listing undated (Box 22)
    - Michigan Mail (print-outs) 2002 (Box 22)
    - Office of Communications News Releases 2002 (Box 22)
    - Sharfman Memorial Lecture 1969 (Box 22)
  - Newsletters
    - Alumni Bulletin
      - 1942-1943 vol. 1-2 (Box 6)
      - 1967-1969 vol. 3-4 (Box 6)
    - Bulletin
      - 1965-1967 vol. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Common Bonds Spring 1994-Winter 2006, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Computing Services Newsletter
      - 1985 vol. 1 (Box 6)
    - Dividend
      - 1969-1989 vol. 1-20, 20 folders (Box 6)
      - 1990-1998 vol. 21-29, 9 folders (Box 7)
      - 2001-2004 (vols. 32-35) (Box 21)
        (bound volume)
      - 2005-(vol. 36-) (Box 21)
    - Focus on the Computer, undated (Box 7)
    - Human Resource Management, v. 14 no. 4, 1975 v. 17 1978 (Box 7)
    - Info: An Information Resources Gazette, 1991-1992 (Box 7)
    - Michigan Business Review
      - 1949-1964 vol. 1-16, 16 volumes (Box 7)
      - 1965-1974 vol. 17-26, 1 folders; 5 volumes (Box 8)
        [Title changes to University of Michigan Business Review]
    - Monroe Street Journal Weekly
      - 1979-1982 (Box 8)
    - Newsletter
      - 1965-1985 vol. 1-20, 9 folders (Box 8)
      - 1985-1993 vol. 21-29 (Box 8)
    - Occasional Papers
      - 1980 vol. 1 (Box 8)
    - University of Michigan Business Review
      - 1975-1979 vol. 27-31, 5 folders (Box 8)
    - Weekly Newsletter for Faculty and Staff, 1965 vol 1 (Box 8)
  - Proceedings
    - Area Development Institute 1953 (Box 8)
    - Arthur Young Professor's Roundtable 1977 (Box 8)
    - 1977 Business Leadership Award, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Programs
    - Awards Program 1961-1964 (Box 9)
    - Commencement Programs 1976-1987, 1993, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Convocations 1949 (Box 9)
    - Dedication of the Assembly Hall 1972 (Box 9)
    - Honors Banquet 1972 (Box 9)
    - Newcomer's Dinner 1984 (Box 9)
    - Reunion and Event Programs (Box 22)
  - Proposals
    - Advanced Management Center: A Presentation for the General Motors Corporation, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Project on Serials Analysis for Business Administration Library Description and Proposal, undated (Box 9)
    - Proposed Projects for the Graduate School of Business Administration, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Reports
    - About the School of Business Administration 1985-1998 (Box 22)
    - Budget Planning 1988-1989 (Box 9)
    - Changing Organizational Cultures: Prism 4, An Assessment Instrument; Prism 5, A Change Workbook, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Competitive Positioning, 1988-1989 (Box 9)
    - DMC Participant Profile 1980-1981 (Box 9)
    - Europe 1992 Challenge to American Business, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Financial Disclosure Practices of the American Cities: A Public Report, 1976 (Box 9)
    - First Things First: A Business and Design Educational Experiment, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Fortran Applications in Business Administration, [1970] (Box 9)
    - Fortran Case Studies Illustrating Fundamental Business Applications, 1969 (Box 9)
    - An Investment in Excellence, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Marketing Research Report: Michigan High School Guidance Counselors Perceptions of the University of Michigan, 1990 (Box 9)
    - The Michigan BBA Employment Survey
      - 1981-1982, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
    - The Michigan BBA Placement Report
      - 1990, 1993 (Box 9)
    - The Michigan MBA Employment Survey
      - 1981-1983, 1986 (Box 9)
    - The Michigan MBA Placement Report
      - 1990, 1993, 1995 (Box 9)
    - The Michigan Placement Report, 1996-1997, 1999-2000 (Box 9)
    - Report of the Bachelor of Business Administration Degree Study Committee, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Report of the MBA Degree Study Committee, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Report Prepared for the Accreditation Visitation Team of the American Association of Collegiate Schools of Business, 1970 (Box 9)
    - School of Business Administration Background Information 1991 (Box 9)
    - Second Venezuelan Student Leader Seminar in Economics and Business, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Self Evaluation of Accounting Program 1984 (Box 10)
    - Taxes and Plant Location in Michigan, 1957 (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan--Aid Brazilian Program at the Instituto Tecnologico de Aeronautica, 1967 (Box 10)
    - Update: Report of the Graduate School of Business Administration
      - 1979/1980-1982/1983, 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Investor's Report 2001-2002 (Box 22)
  - Statistics
    - Miscellaneous 1976-1988 (Box 10)
    - Size of Class, 1964/65-1965/66 (Box 10)
    - Student Credit Hours and Direct Costs, 1964-1966 (Box 10)
  - Yearbooks
    - The Blue Chip, 1986/87 (Box 10)
    - The Global Blue, 1996-1999, 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Photo Book, 1993-1996, 1998, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - Memorandum, 1983 (Box 10)
    - UMBS 2001 A B-School Odyssey, 2001 (Box 10)
- Sub-Unit Publications
  - Actuarial Program
    - Brochures 1953, undated (Box 10)
    - Directories
      - Directory of Alumni of the Actuarial Program, 1953-1979 (Box 10)
    - Newsletters
      - Actuarial Newsletter, 1974-1979 (Box 10)
  - Actuarial Science Fellowship Fund
    - Annual Reports 1962-1967 (Box 10)
    - Brochures undated (Box 10)
  - Bank Training Program
    - Brochures 1952-1953 (Box 10)
  - Bureau of Business Research
    - Brochures
      - Miscellaneous undated, 1948-1971 (Box 10)
    - Catalogs
      - Michigan Research and Business Bibliography, 1963-1965 (Box 10)
      - Publications of the Bureau of Business Research, 1950-[1970] (Box 10)
      - Regional Economic Growth and Development: Recent Publications and Current Research, [ca. 1962] (Box 10)
      - Research and Publications Pertaining to Business Development in Michigan, [ca. 1961] (Box 10)
    - Newsletters
      - Business Service Newsletter
        - 1951-1952 n.16-21 (Box 10)
    - Proceedings
      - Michigan Advertising Papers
        - 1957-1959 1-3 (Box 10)
      - Michigan Business Papers
        - 1937-1964 no. 1-40 (Box 11)
          (1 bound volume and 13 folders)
        - 1965-1968 no. 41-48, 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Reports
      - Activities Report of the Bureau of Business Research, 1970 (Box 11)
      - Financial Laws and their Effect Upon the Economic Expansion of Michigan, 1969 (Box 11)
      - The Housing Status of Married Students at the University of Michigan, 1939 (Box 11)
      - Michigan Business Cases
        [Continued under the heading "Division of Research"]
        - 1930-1931 1-4, 7 (Box 11)
      - Michigan Business Reports
        - 1937-1949 no. 1-16, 4 folders (Box 11)
        - 1949-1968 no. 17-56, 15 folders (Box 12)
      - Michigan Business Studies
        - 1926-1934 vol. 1-6, 6 volumes (Box 12)
        - 1935-1941 vol. 7-9, 3 volumes (Box 13)
        - 1942-1958 vol. 10-13, 6 folders (Box 13)
        - 1958-1971 vol. 14-18, 5 folders (Box 14)
      - Michigan in the 1970s An Economic Forecast, 1964 (Box 14)
      - Standards for Education and Experience for Certified Public Accountants, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Survey of Ann Arbor Housing with Special Reference to Student Accommodation, 1945 (Box 14)
      - Working Papers, 1970-1972 [Continued under the heading "Division of Research"] (Box 14)
  - Business and Industrial Assistance Division
    - Brochures undated (Box 15)
    - Proposals
      - Community Stabilization and Revitalization (CSR): Enhancing Economic and Social Quality of Life in Flint/Genesee, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
      - Flint/Genesee Manufacturing Firm Assistance Center, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Center for International Business Education
    - Bibliography and Handbooks
      - Business Cases on Emerging Economies, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Teaching Global Managers About Global Change, 1994 (Box 22)
    - Brochures
      - Miscellaneous undated (Box 15)
    - Manuals
      - Internationalism and Multiculturalism in Management Education: A Curriculum Development Handbook, 1992 (Box 15)
      - Language, Study and International Business: A Handbook for Students, [1991] (Box 15)
    - Programs
      - Southeast Asia Business Research Conference 1996 (Box 15)
    - Reports
      - Anyone Can Export:
        - Automotive Components Six Michigan Companies Show You How 1992 (Box 15)
        - Eleven Michigan Companies Show You How 1991 (Box 15)
      - CIBER Information Update, 1990 (Box 15)
      - International Training at Michigan: A Survey of Area and Language Studies Graduates, 1992 (Box 15)
    - Bibliography and Handbooks
      - Business Cases on Emerging Economies, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Teaching Global Managers About Global Change, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Computer and Information Systems Program
    - Course Descriptions and Miscellaneous, Winter 1989 (Box 22)
  - Computing Services
    - Brochures
      - Free Students MTS Request Accounts, 1994 (Box 15)
  - Dearborn Campus--Division of Business Administration
    - Proposals
      - Proposal for a Master of Management Degree Program 1971 (Box 15)
      - A Proposed New Graduate Program in Industrial Management, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Division of Management Education
    - Brochures
      - Miscellaneous undated, 1975-1983 (Box 15)
    - Bulletins
      - Management Programs 1980-1984 (Box 15)
      - Management Seminars
        - 1973-1983, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Newsletters
      - Human Resource Management
        - 1973 vol. 12 (Box 15)
  - Division of Research
    - Catalogs
      - Books in Print, [1972-1973] (Box 15)
      - Michigan Business and Economic Research Bibliography, 1967-1977 (Box 15)
      - Research Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
    - Journals
      - Current Issues and Research in Advertising, 1978-1986, 1988, 6 folders (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Brochures (Box 16)
      - Essays in Honor of William A. Paton: Pioneering Accounting Theorist, 1979 (Box 16)
      - Words! Combining Fun and Learning (by William A. Paton), 1984 (Box 16)
    - Newsletters
      - IBROM (Independent Business Research Office of Michigan), 1983 (Box 16)
      - The Ph.D. Forum, 1988 vol. 1 (Box 16)
      - The Research Beat, 1987-1993 (Box 16)
    - Proceedings
      - Minorities at the Crossroads: Selected Proceedings of the Third and Fourth Annual Symposiums on the State of the Black Economy, 1973, 1974 (Box 16)
      - New Dimensions of Appropriate Technology: Selected Proceedings of the 1979 Symposium, 1979 (Box 16)
    - Reports
      - Black Economic Development Analysis and Implications--An Anthology, 1975 (Box 16)
      - CPA Firm Viability: A Study of Major Environmental Factors Affecting Firms of Various Sizes and Characteristics, 1979 (Box 16)
      - Database Systems Research Group Prospectus, 1978 (Box 16)
      - Michigan Business Papers
        - 1977-1985 63-67, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Michigan Business Reports
        - 1967-1979 57-63 and n.s. 1, 4 folders (Box 16)
        - [Numbers 1-56 will be found under Bureau of Business Research] (Box 16)
      - Michigan Business Studies
        - 1975-1982 vol. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Michigan International Business Studies
        - 1981 no. 17 (Box 16)
      - Michigan Management and Executive Development Studies
        - 1987 no. 5 (Box 16)
      - Michigan's Management and Executive Development Studies
        - 1984-1985 1-3 (Box 16)
      - The Newly Promoted Executive: A Study in Corporate Leadership, 1980/81-1983/84, 1985/86-1986/87, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Report of the Research and Publication Activities of the Division of Research
        - 1974/1975-1977/1978 (Box 17)
        - 1980/1981-1982/1983 (Box 17)
      - Tax Executive Compensation and Organization of the Tax Function Within the Firm: A Survey of Tax Executives Institute Members, 1976 (Box 17)
      - Working Papers
        - 1980 [Previously under "Bureau of Business Research"] (Box 17)
  - Executive Development Program
    - Brochures
      - undated 1954-1981, 6 folders (Box 17)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1987 undated (Box 17)
        - circa 1979 (Box 22)
      - Program for Management Development: Managing Critical Issues, 1992-1993 (Box 17)
  - Executive Education Center
    - Bulletins
      - Executive Programs and Management Seminars
        - 1988-1999 (Box 17)
      - Management Programs 1986-1987 (Box 17)
    - Newsletters
      - The Executive Report
        - 1988-1993 (vol. 1 1-5, vol. 2 1) (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous
      - circa 1987-2000 (Box 22)
    - Programs
      - January-December 2001 (Box 22)
      - July 2002-June 2003 (Box 22)
      - July 2003-June 2004 (Box 22)
      - January-December 2005 (Box 22)
      - Undated (Box 22)
  - Executive Program
    - Brochures 1981-1986 (Box 17)
  - Global Leadership Program circa 1987-1991 (Box 22)
  - Hospital Administration Program
    - Bulletins
      - 1956/1957-1967/1968, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Institute for Entrepreneurial Studies
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
      (Includes issues of MEntrpeneur and InCompany)
  - Institute for International Commerce
    - Brochures
      - Advanced Management Program in Megeve, France, 1969 (Box 17)
      - Seminars 1967-1976 (Box 17)
    - Directories
      - Michigan Directory of Importers, 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - Law, History and Communications Department
    - Course Offerings 1999-2000 (Box 22)
  - Leadership, Education and Development (LEAD)
    - Programs
      - LEAD Opening Dinner 1987 (Box 17)
    - Yearbooks
      - Conquest, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Michigan Bankers Association
    - Directories
      - The Michigan Club, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Michigan Graduate School of Bank Management
    - Brochures 1978-1979 (Box 17)
  - Multidisciplinary Action Projects (MAP)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Office of Admissions and Student Services
    - MBA Application and Financial Aid Information, [1982] (Box 17)
  - Office of Development and Alumni Relations
    - Directories
      - Class of 1951
        - 45th Year Reunion Class Notes, 1996 (Box 18)
      - Class of 1970
        - School Class Notes 1970, undated (Box 18)
      - Class of 1971
        - 25th Year Reunion Class Notes, 1996 (Box 18)
    - Directories
      - Class of 1972
        - '72 Class Notes, 1998 (Box 18)
      - Class of 1985
        - Class Notes 1985, undated (Box 18)
      - Class of 1986
        - 10th Year Reunion Class Notes, 1996 (Box 18)
      - Class of 1987
        - 10th Year Reunion Class Notes, 1998 (Box 18)
      - Class of 1991
        - 5th Year Reunion Class Notes, 1996 (Box 18)
      - Class of 1992
        - 5th Year Reunion Class Notes, 1998 (Box 18)
      - Class of 1995
        - 1st Year Reunion Class Notes, 1996 (Box 18)
      - Class of 1996
        - 1st Year Reunion Class Notes, 1996 (Box 18)
  - Personnel Office
    - Newsletters
      - Management Development Bulletin, 1962-1963 (Box 19)